Sync by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Okay.
Burn unit. commence.
You go first.
Oh. I play soccer. 'cause
I forgot I have hands.
Burn! I'm on the news.
because I have a huge head.
Burn!
I can't outrun a lawnmower
'cause my dress is so tight.
Oh! I'm dead.
Burn.
Whoa.
It's Banjo.
Oh. I'm a cowboy. and I got...
Wait. wait. wait.
Suspend burn unit.
This is a great movie.
It's a Spaguetti Western.
the best one. underappreciated.
He plays a Banjo.
Yeah. I can see that.
And they made a
whole bunch of these.
Dad. Do we have anything
bigger than this?
Oh. Gene. what'd you do?
Nothing. yet. Just
planning ahead.
What are you guys watching?
Nothing.
Go back to bed.
The burn unit is just me and dad.
Whoa! Did he just shoot
bullets out of his Banjo?
Yes.
Damn!
Oh. you like that. Gene? 'Cause
we're changing the channel.
No. no. Let's watch it.
This is pretty much
the beginning.
What? What?!
Gene. sit here.
It's like pushing
a couch off the couch!
Yah!
Here.
Hold my plunger.
- Yah!
- Ow!
Oh!
We are just so thrilled
that you chose us
to cater the event.
Mom. mom... fill me up.
I just hope we can live up
to last year's event. Mom.
That Colleen Caviello. mom...
She really outdid herself.
And never lets anyone
forget about it.
Just fill up the little mug.
Ouch.
Right. Right. right.
Okay. Mr. Frond.
Good-bye. Good-bye.
So what are we catering?
That sounded promising.
Oh. it's a real big deal. Bobby.
It's a fund-raiser for Tina's
conflict resolution club.
Colleen Caviello made
the food last year.
This year she can go...
Blow a balloon.
Yay! You're catering
our fund-raiser.
That's great.
How much does it pay?
Nothing.
Nothing?
It's a benefit. Bobby.
It's a spaghetti dinner.
But we don't make spaghetti.
This is school fund-raising.
Bob... it's a pasta game.
You make spaghetti.
or you go home.
Besides. it's for a good cause.
Oh. yeah... to one-up
Colleen Caviello.
That's a. that's a great cause.
You weren't there. Bob!
You don't know how awful it was.
This is delicious.
Oh my God.
I love this ziti.
They love my ziti.
And that was the worst
day of my life.
Anyway. this isn't about
Colleen. this is about Tina.
We're raising money to buy
a bulletproof trash can
so gang members can finally
throw out their guns. Aw.
And we're teaching conflict
resolution skills
you can use in your own lives.
That's right. Tina.
And Mr. Frond is running
the whole thing.
Ugh. Mr. Frond?
He's a tall drink of...
Annoying.
That may be true. but you're
gonna drink that drink. mister.
I don't want to.
I have worked too hard
to get us this event.
so you'll be nice to Frond.
and you'll make spaghetti
and meatballs!
No... no...
Yes... yes!
Fine. but I'm gonna half-ass it.
Yay.
Dad. check it out.
Little princess guitar.
Gene. that's mine!
You never use it.
I'm like Banjo.
What's the bad guy's name?
Ceviche.
Ceviche. yeah.
He reminds me of this kid
at school... Choo-Choo.
Choo-Choo?
Yeah. He's kind of my Nemesis.
If I'm telling a joke. he'll say
the punch line before I do.
A vampire walks
into a bar and says
I'll have a...
I'll have a blood lite.
Huh?
What do you call a Spanish guy
with a rubber toe?
Roberto! Rober...
What kind of bees make milk?
Boo-bees!
So. I'm gonna use this guitar
to stand up to Choo-Choo
like Banjo.
That's. uh...
That's great. Gene.
But I think your face is wrong.
My face is wrong?!
Yeah. you should
do the Banjo icy stare.
Like this?
No. Not like that.
No. no. no.
Don't growl. That...
Like this?
Hmm.
Maybe try that.
Is Choo-Choo scared
of stroke victims?
Terrified.
Hey. Gene. Gene.
How do you plead?
I'm innocent.
Your fingerprints
were all over the murder weapon.
I don't have fingers.
Your honor!
I don't have time for this.
What?! You don't have time
for food court?
Where are you going?
Hey. Wanna hear
a good one?
What's green and sings?
Go ahead. Do it.
El...
Ah.
Elvis P...
Elvis Par...
Ah!
Forget it.
I'll tell you
what's green and sings...
Elvis Parsley.
You don't say the punch lines
to other people's jokes anymore.
You got that. Poo-Poo?
What the hell?
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you. everyone.
Thank you.
Anyway... Gene. look.
They're about
to announce the verdict.
Guilty.
No!
Take him away.
Gene. where are you going?
What's up with Gene?
I don't know. Lasagna.
I don't know.
You know. cooking spaghetti
isn't even cooking.
It's just. like. boiling water.
Hey. Bobby. can I
come to this thing?
Uh. I don't think so.
Why not? Some
of these moms
are divorced. right?
They meet me. I meet their kids.
Maybe throw the ball around.
Not inside. but...
uh. we agreed no more
school events for you. Teddy.
Hey. dad. Guess what?
What?
I acted like Banjo
and took Choo-Choo down.
Everyone laughed.
Well. one kid laughed.
Peter Pescadero.
He has a learning disability.
Yeah. but he knows what's funny.
Now that you
stood up for yourself...
Oh. congratulations. Gene...
Can we stop talking about it?
Okay. tonight. I propose.
dad. that after everyone else
goes to bed... Gene...
We fire up the burn unit
and we watch Canine Criminals.
and then that stretching show.
and then maybe a little
Beetlejuice in Español.
Beetlejugo. Beetlejugo.
Beetlejugo.
Ay. ay. ay. ay!
I would. except a certain
best dad in the world
went out and got this!
It's the complete Banjo box set!
All 12 DVDs and over
28 hours of extras.
Yeah!
28 hours?!
Dad. can I... see that
fork for a minute?
Um... here.
Thank you.
And I just want to...
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey!
No!
Best part right here. Gene.
There's only gonna be two shots.
me shooting you.
and then me drinking
this shot of whiskey.
Wow.
Oh. what a line.
Go ahead.
watch your stupid movie.
There are other people for me
to hang out with around here.
Tina. get up.
Let's hang out.
Okay. Maybe we can
practice conflict resolution.
Say something mean to me
so I can not react.
Anything I want?
Yeah.
Ha-ha!
Well. uh. your room looks
like it was decorated
by a perverted jockey.
When you say that. what I feel
is that you're trying
to hurt my feelings.
Oh. my God.
Why do you talk so...
Slow?
When you say that. what I feel
is that you're trying to hurt...
Oh man. Tina.
This is really. really boring.
Okay. well...
Hey. mom. you want to hang out?
Oh. I'd love that!
Oh. mother-daughter
bonding time.
Just like me and my mother.
Ooh! Makeover!
Hmm...
Okay. my little cowpokes.
Time for school.
You can watch the rest tonight.
Mom!
How could you?
How could I what?
How could you encourage this?
Oh. Louise. don't be a pill.
A little father-son bonding
is going on here
and that's a good thing.
These two don't
always do it so well.
Tambourine solo!
Sheesh.
All right. this is how
you throw a spiral.
You ready?
Here comes a bullet.
Hmm.
Oh. stupid ball!
It's 'cause there's no laces.
I'm hungry.
All right. we're done.
Go inside.
I want peanut butter!
It turns out we bond
better over movies
that I like to watch.
that I make Gene watch.
Yeah.
Oh. that's...
That's adorable.
I'm going to school.
Good.
Great.
Why don't you learn something
and become a lawyer.
Abs: The conflict
resolution program
sweeping our school.
You all know my system.
and at the spaghetti dinner.
so will your parents
or legal guardians.
um. Becky.
'cause your mom's in jail.
Tina. Jocelyn. Jimmy junior...
let's rehearse.
Becky. you just watch.
Tina here just found out
that her best friend Jocelyn
told Jimmy junior
that Tina. is "whack."
And... acting.
Tina. Jocelyn
told me you are whack.
Jocelyn. you skank.
I hate you.
Whatever. It's true.
You are whack.
And... freeze!
Well. that resolved nothing.
Let's rewind. shall we?
Let's work out
our abs. A!
Access your feelings!
When you gossiped about
me to Jimmy junior.
it hurt my feelings.
B: Be apologetic!
Sorry.
S: Slap it!
Well done.
Do it just like that
at the dinner.
Oh. enjoy your lunch. everyone.
If you ever gossip about me
to Jimmy junior outside
of a conflict resolution skit.
I'll punch you in the face.
It was just a skit. Tina.
I will punch you.
Again and again.
and again and again...
My God. what a psycho.
And again and again...
And again and again and...
Well. the important thing is.
I shared this movie with Gene
and it helped him stand up
for himself at school.
Eh. I beat up a lot of kids
like Gene when I was his age.
Not that I was a bully...
just kids like Gene. you know?
That get beat up.
Bob. how are
the meatballs comin'?
Because they need to be perfect.
Hey. it's just like your
burgers. only spherical!
Hey!
Hey. what?
They're not for you.
They're for me to show off
in front of the other moms
at the fund-raiser.
Bobby. make one extra-big
for Colleen Caviello to choke on.
Okay.
All right. looks like
I'm sitting with you today.
Me. then either of you.
Which sticker do you like better.
my purple ladybug
or Susie's red one?
And good-bye.
Hey there.
Spew-Spew.
Funny seeing you here.
In the cafeteria during lunch?
Yeah.
Why do you keep doing that?
Keep doing what?
You're weird!
Weird? I think you mean
anti-hero.
Look at the hat.
It's mom's sun hat. you dork.
You like finishing my jokes.
Well. finish my food.
Gene. you are being
a class act jerk.
This is all about jokes
from your stupid joke book.
You've insulted Jokes for
Blokes for the last time.
Oh. don't you even
think about it. Gene.
Food fight!
No...!
And these two. Bob. were
throwing at each other.
I hate you.
They seem to be in conflict.
I'm sure we can.
uh. work through it.
I'd like you to take
a look at my abs.
Um. no thank you.
Show him your abs. Mr. Frond.
We'd all like to see your abs.
Okay.
I really don't.
And your ding-dong.
Gene.
Gene. why don't you access
how it makes you feel
that Louise is angry with you.
Fine.
That's all I'm gonna say.
Well. this is all I'm gonna say.
Hi-yah!
Let go of my...
H-hey.
L-Louise. Louise. Louise.
You're not using your abs.
Um. this is dumb.
Bo... Bob.
Yes.
When you say "this is dumb."
it makes me feel like
pinching you in the eye.
Why did you do that?
So we can resolve this
and set a good example
for your children.
Okay.
I will now kick you in the shin.
Okay. Okay.
All right.
Hey!
Don't throw
repressed memory Emily!
She won't remember this.
Well. this is really
working out. Mr. Frond.
Your system is amazing.
Ho. No. no. no. no. no.
We're gonna go.
You know what I forgot to say?
Detention! Detention!
And you.
I am gonna cut you!
I am gonna cut you out of
the conflict resolution
spaghetti dinner!
Wha... oh. come on. you can't...
Too late! The conflict
resolution spaghetti dinner
will now be
a conflict resolution fast.
Well. that didn't go so well.
Mm-mm.
Yeah. he seemed angry.
Frothy.
And kind of bloated. right?
Mm.
Maybe he's dehydrated.
Your mother's gonna kill me.
So glad we had
a chance to talk this out!
Emily. I'm sorry!
Detention?!
And we're banned from
catering the peace club dinner!
Bobby!
I'm sorry. Lin. I...
I can't even tell you
how many favors I had to
call in to cater that thing.
How many?
Two!
Tina. you're supposed
to be watching the restaurant.
I'm too upset to serve food.
W-what'd you do?
Did you lock up?
Yes.
Were there customers inside?
I don't know.
No one's gonna come
to the fund-raiser now.
Good job. Bobby!
It's not my fault. Lin.
It was
Mr. Frond's fault.
And Louise's.
And Gene's!
And most of all.
that stupid movie.
Hey!
Hey. don't blame the movie.
All right.
Leave bingo out of this!
Shut up!
All of you!
I'm locking these movies
in my jewelry drawer.
Aw. come on.
Unfair!
'Bout time.
You're overreacting. Lin.
The hell I am!
I'm in charge of
a spaghetti dinner
that's not gonna have
any spaghetti!
If we all just
worked on our abs...
Not now with that crap. Tina!
I can't believe I got detention.
If I were you.
I would teach Gene a lesson
he'll never forget.
I had a perfect record.
And then you tainted it.
Taint.
Looks like you got Choo-Choo
right where you want him.
Just give him that icy stare
with some little princess
and finish him.
You want a little of this?
Oh. Oh. yeah. he wants it.
Now give him the icy stare.
Put him in his place.
You're dead!
Quiet!
♪ Sexual. sexual ♪
Okay. well. I'm gonna go get
Gene and Louise from detention.
Great! Bring some meatballs.
Got plenty of meatballs.
All dressed up and nowhere to go.
Mmm.
Meatball. Mmm.
All right.
I'm gonna leave.
Gene. this happens now!
Uh. how are we doing this?
Staring contest?
Joke-off?
Kick his ass.
Choo-Choo!
Why are their shirts off?
Oh. boy.
I didn't want to do this.
I haven't even pressed
the blue button yet.
I don't even know what sound...
Fight! Fight!
Fight...! Stop.
There's not gonna be a fight.
Oh. thank God.
Let me go!
This train is off the tracks.
Choo-Choo!
Oh. I get the name now.
I always thought
it was 'cause of how he chewed.
'Cause he chews like a train.
Hey. calm down.
Let's go home. Gene.
You touching my kid?
Sorry. What?
I said. you touching my kid?
Oh. he was attacking my kid.
Oh. yeah? Good.
What is going on with the shirts?
I'm gonna beat your ass so bad
I can skip the gym tonight.
- Dad. this is bad.
- Fight! Fight!
Thank you. Louise.
Fight! Fight...!
I have it under control.
This happens now!
Kill him!
Run!
I can't.
I've got this friggin'
guitar around my neck!
Ha!
Oh. Gene. push down.
I'm trying.
- All right.
- Ow.
All right. just so we're clear.
we're not hiding from those guys.
We're respectfully
declining their invitation
for a fight. okay?
Right.
No. thank you.
I would absolutely
get into a fight
under the right
circumstances. if...
What's that smell?
Oh. Gene!
Gene!
I'm sorry! Hey. shh. shh.
I hear them.
They're coming.
Real...?
You-you hear them?
Gotcha.
Louise. enough.
You've been stirring the pot
for three days.
and acting like a baby.
Now you owe your brother
an apology
for getting him in trouble.
Me?!
Both of you owe me an apology.
Both of us? Why?
Because we wanted to watch Banjo?
Because you stopped
hanging out with me.
What? Shh.
Use your slide voices.
First. the burn unit
stopped hanging out.
Then. the lunch bunch
God. we have lame names.
Who the hell am
I gonna hang around.
if not you two?
Mom and Tina... the
menstruation nation?
Ugh! That's a really
bad name.
You're all I've got.
Louise. I'm sorry.
Me. too. Don't cry.
Ha! Got you.
You thought I was really crying.
Gross.
Gene. stop.
Oh. my God.
I can't help it.
It's anxiety.
And turkey jerky.
It's so incredible.
Your farts smell like mine.
Really?
Oh. great. Are you
guys bonding again?
I'm sorry. but that's
a huge discovery.
A fart is like a fingerprint.
and we have the
same fingerprints.
High-five.
Ugh! Put your hand up.
All right.
I swear my farts smell
like your farts. dad.
I don't think so. Louise.
Oh. wait.
Wait. wait. wait. wait.
Huh?
No. That smells
like your mom's.
No!
Oh. your mom.
What are we gonna do
about mom and Tina?
They could live in here with us!
I think I know a better way.
I'm starving.
How embarrassing.
Guess people will be talking
about my baked ziti
for another year.
Guess people will be talking
about my baked ziti
for another year.
Oh. Linda. I didn't see you.
Hi. Coll.
How are you?
Uh...
Thank you.
Tonight. with your help.
we raised over $100.
It was $110.
I warned you. skank!
Whoa. whoa. whoa. whoa.
whoa. whoa. whoa! Girls. please.
It's not time for the skit.
This isn't a skit. It's...
This is real life.
Last year.
the only fighting was to
get seconds on my ziti!
Okay. that's it. Colleen.
Let me tell you about that ziti.
That sauce was store-bought.
and you know it.
Ladies. please!
I thought I told you. Bob.
You and your spaghetti
aren't welcome here.
But I want to say something.
No. thank you.
I've had enough
of your hurt speech.
Would it make
a difference if I...
Worked on my abs?
Oh.
I want to... a...
What was a again?
Anus.
Amyl nitrate.
- Access... I want to access my feelings.
- Mm.
Okay. okay. okay. okay.
enough. enough. enough. enough.
Everyone's about
to kill each other here.
Let's... let's eat!
All right!
Meatballs! Meatballs!
Get your meatballs here.
And spaghetti.
Here. Colleen. why don't you
put these balls in your face?
- Food fight!
- No. no. no...!
Sync by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com